https://www.dpa.hk/data-policy/

Data Policy
Last revised: 26 Feb, 2016
Dragonair Pilots Association is committed to respecting the privacy of our website visitors. The purpose of this policy is to comply with the protection legislation laid out in Cap 486 Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance. This policy outlines how we will treat your personal information.
What Information We Will Collect
We may use, collect and store the following types of information:
i. information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, including your IP address, location, browser type, length of visit and number of page views for web traffic analysis
ii. information that you provide to the Association for the purpose of registering your membership with us
iii. information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, message boards, email notifications and/or newsletters
iv. other information that you choose to send to us
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file which is placed on your device. Cookies help to analyse web traffic and allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. Certain cookies may contain personal data – for example, if you click to “remember me” when logging in, a cookie may store your username. Most cookies won’t collect personal data that identifies you, and will instead collect more general information, such as how users arrive at and use our Sites, or a user’s general location.
What do we use cookies for?
We may place cookies or similar files on your device for security purposes, to tell us whether you have visited the site before, to otherwise facilitate site navigation, and to personalise your experience while visiting our site. Cookies allow us to collect technical and navigational information, such as browser type, time spent on our site and pages visited. Cookies also allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the site. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting the site. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better site by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your device or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
What kinds of cookies do we use?
Generally, the cookies that are used on the site can be broken down in to the following categories:
Session cookies
These cookies are used ‘in-session’ each time you visit and then expire when you leave a site or shortly thereafter: they are not stored on your device permanently, do not contain any personal data and help by minimising the need to transfer personal data across the internet. These cookies can be deleted or you can refuse to allow their use, but this will hamper the performance and your experience in using the Sites. These cookies also take time stamps that record when you access a site and when you leave a site.
Tracking cookies
These cookies enable us to recognise repeat visitors to our site. By matching an anonymous, randomly generated identifier, a tracking cookie keeps track of where a user of our site came from, what search engine they may have used, what link they clicked on, what keyword they used and where they were in the world when they accessed a site. By monitoring this data, we can make improvements to our site.
Persistent cookies
This type of cookie is saved on your device for a fixed period (sometimes for a few hours, sometimes for a year or longer) and is not deleted when the browser is closed. Persistent cookies are used where we need to remember who you are for more than one browsing session. For example, this type of cookie can be used to store your preferences, so that they are remembered for the next visit to a Site.
Performance or analytical cookies
Performance cookies are used to analyse how the site are used and to monitor their performance, which allows us to improve your experience in using the site. These cookies help us to tailor the content of the site to reflect what the site users find most interesting and to identify when technical issues with the site arise. We may also use this data to compile reports to help us to analyse how the site is used, what the most common issues are and how we can improve the site.
Can the cookies be blocked?
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you would prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers will allow you to: (i) change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it; (ii) to disable existing cookies; or (iii) to set your browser to automatically reject any cookies. However, please be aware that if you disable or reject cookies, some features and services on our site may not work properly because we may not be able to recognise and associate you with your DPA account. In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests.
Use of your personal data
We may use your personal information to:
i. administer the website
ii. improve your browsing experience by personalising the website
iii. enable your use of the services available on the website
iv. send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you
v. send you general communications
vi. send you any email notifications which you have specifically requested
vii. send to you communications relating to our business to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require any communications)
viii. provide our contracted website agency only with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user and will NOT be used for any third party marketing
ix. deal with enquiries and complaints
Service providers we use
All our electronic financial application transactions and records are handled by Xero Ltd. For further information on Xero please visit www.xero.com
All our outbound bulk email is handled by Mailchimp, part of The Rocket Science Group. For further information on Mailchimp please visit www.mailchimp.com
All our email accounts and working platforms are handled by Google. For further information on Google please visit www.google.com
All our surveys are handled by Survey Monkey. For further information on Survey Monkey please visit www.surveymonkey.com
For the transfer and passing of API information between various application we use Zapier inc. For further information on Zapier please visit www.zapier.com
Google Analytics
We may use Google Analytics to analyse your use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical information about website usage. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available here www.google.com
Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose information about you:
i. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
ii. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
iii. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention
Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. Our servers are hosted by HostNine LLC, www.hostnine.com
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential.
DPA.HK website
The dpa.hk website is protected by SSL ensuring encrypted communication between your device and our server. We use a Comodo 256 bit RSA domain validation certificate. You can check the authenticity of our certificate by visiting www.comodo.com
HKALPA
We are affiliated with IFALPA through HKALPA and in accordance with IFALPA regulations we will share your data with HKALPA. Your data will be held by HKALPA in accordance with their data and privacy policies. You can find information on their policies www.hkalpa.org
Policy Amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you in accordance with Section 18 of the ordinance. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee.
Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
Contacting the DPA
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us at Dragonair Pilots Association, Room 502, Chung Sheung Building, 9 Queen Victoria Street, Central, Hong Kong
0
×
Member Application
Complete the form and enjoy the benefits brought by DPA!
1 Personal Info2 Job Info
Name*
First
Last
KA ERN*Enter your KA ERN.Password*
Enter Password
Confirm Password
Email*
Mobile Phone*Hong Kong mobile phone number only.Public Profile
Allow mobile number and email address to be visible to other members
Date of Birth*Day12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031Month123456789101112Year202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965196419631962196119601959195819571956195519541953195219511950194919481947194619451944194319421941194019391938193719361935193419331932193119301929192819271926192519241923192219211920Gender*MaleFemale
Date of Joining*Day12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031Month123456789101112Year202120202019201820172016201520142013201220112010200920082007200620052004200320022001200019991998199719961995199419931992199119901989198819871986198519841983198219811980197919781977197619751974197319721971197019691968196719661965196419631962196119601959195819571956195519541953195219511950194919481947194619451944194319421941194019391938193719361935193419331932193119301929192819271926192519241923192219211920Contract*Local AExpat BStandard ContractCOS 18Rank*CaptainS/OJFOF/OFleet*A320/1A330KA Crew MailboxOptional, but please let us know if you have it.Terms and Conditions*
I agree to the Terms and Conditions
CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
Forget Password
Please provide your KA ERN. The new password will be sent to your registered email address.
KA ERN:
Reset My Password
Back to top
